[Music]
Hello to all of you, in this video I am going to
tell you how to make a Universal Tumko motor policy claim.
So first of all, if you want to make an
online claim mission for Universal Tumko, then you can go
to the Universal Pump site
using a web browser. If you do
n't want to do it through a web browser, then
its toll free number is there. Look, it is
visible here, okay, 1800
224030, okay, or another number is visible
here, one double zero, okay, two double zero.
You can call on this toll free number and
give your details, then the
online collection will be done. If their number is not
connecting or the phone is not connecting or
you are not calling from anyone else, then you can use another
option.
Look, here you will see the
option of Motor Claim Intimation. Okay, then an
option like Motor Limited will come,
what will you do, click on it, okay,
click, then it will proceed.
After clicking on Motor, you will get an option like this,
see the policy number here, which is the
policy number of your vehicle.  You have to
enter it here. After entering the policy number, you have to
enter the name of the injured. Name of the injured
means the name of the person in whose name the policy
is, you have to enter it. Then enter the
registered mobile number which is of the policy,
that is fine. Alternate number, any other number,
mobile number, okay. Email
ID has to be entered, the email ID is theirs, okay,
and the registered number means the vehicle
registration number, whatever it is, CG 04
ABCD one two three five, whatever it is,
Indian number, put the last five digital, it will work. Put the
last last five digital,
okay. State, as soon as you click here,
many options will open for you. This
evening it is Chandigarh, right? Whichever state you
belong to, you can
know that state as state, CG, so CG is Chhattisgarh and
Maharashtra, it comes like this,
after that you will click on the state,
your city of that state will open, you will
click here, okay, after clicking on it, you will
select the data, accident means the
day on which the car met with an accident,
you have to enter it here, okay. The time during which the car met with an
accident has to be entered here. I was
driving at that time.  The
name of the driver who was driving the car has to be entered in the accident location will also be
in the location that will be of the district and the
town which will come within the district,
you have to enter that in the location okay
nature of class if there is third party damage in the car
then third part will be entered if there is
damage to the car if it is theft then the
option will come in theft only or
third party loss will come, ATP loss will come,
whatever comes then in ODI only
damage to the car will be recorded and third DP will be done
okay if there is a fracture on the hand then it will be done
typical if you click here then the
name of the garage will come up showroom whichever comes, enter it
okay after that intimate means
if you have entered this form online then
you have to enter his name if the customer has filled it himself then you have to
enter your own name after that
contact number is your own contact
number, when you click on it then the option of
dollar and driver and owner comes okay so if the person who is
entering the dollar then he will click on the dollar option
and will
tick it after fixing it see
here how did accident and theft happened
means accident  You have to
enter the full details of what happened here, how the accident happened, for example, suppose
you are going on a journey and
suddenly an animal comes in front of your car, while saving yourself
you hit the divider, then you have to
write in it that I was going on my personal business
and while saving an animal the car
collided with the divider, okay it collided,
after that you have to fix the claim intimation,
okay, if you will do the clarification then it is
possible that it will ask for your registered mobile number,
after asking for the registered mobile number it may
ask you for OTP or
you can also register by entering the capture code directly in it,
okay in this way your claim has been
registered, after the claim is registered
you will be given the claim number,
you will keep it in writing, okay sir will
contact you, after that you have to fill the claim
form, for this we have made a separate video, in that
you will see how we work,
its details have been given,
so if you liked this video of ours, please
like and subscribe to our channel
and share it